ABDULREHMAN

DEVELOPER





053 526 7056



13pfye2046@gmail.com



Nazlah Yamaniyah Jeddah Saudia



https://www.linkedin.com/feed/

PROFILE

I am a qualified and professional web developer with one years of experience in database and website design in react. Strong creative and analytical skills. The combination of React for the front end and Node for the back end is perfect for developing a web application that will handle multiple simultaneous requests. It is also the best technology for creating real-time apps that will process data.

SKILLS

- Tailwind CSS
- Bootstrap
- HTML CSS
- Node
- Ant Design
- JavaScript
- React
- Redux Toolkit
- Photoshop

EDUCATION

INTERMEDIATE EDUCATION

Government College Qila didar Singh July 2017

BACHELOR OF TECHNOLOGY

Bachelor in Computer Science Gift University Gujranwala

2018 - 2020

LANGUAGES

- English
- Urdu

EXPERIENCE

REACT JS DEVELPOR & NODE JS

Phaedra Solutions / Lahore March 2022 - October 2022

- Design and built advanced application .
- Built react app with Bootstrap, Ant Design. Tailwind CSS & React Bootstrap.
- Implementation with Firebase, Mongo DB.
- Using the built-in react toolkit & tailwind toolkit to built a user-
- I have also Implement front-end react to connect backend node and backend connect to Mongo DB.
- Built node application and create a different API and fetch for other server like react application other front-end server & Database server.
- I have good abilities in JavaScript.
- I have one year experience in React Application and six month experience in Node JS.

REACT JS DEVELPOR

Nextep Technology / Islamabad July 2021 - Jan 2022

- Creating front-end and re-useable code .
- scaled Create react application with Materia-UI components & hooks.
- · Performed installation, configuration, and troubleshooting of various software programs.